Guide to the E. Raymond Hall Collection
University of Kansas
Personal Papers of E. Raymond Hall
1890-1983
University of Kansas Kenneth Spencer Research Library University Archives 1450 Poplar Lane, Lawrence, KS 66045-7616 Phone: (785)864-4334 Fax: (785)864-5803 URL: http://spencer.lib.ku.edu
Hall, E. Raymond (Eugene Raymond), 1902-1986
22 linear ft (24 boxes, 1 oversized box, 1 oversized folder)
Hall taught Zoology and was Director of the Natural History Museum at the University of Kansas. This collection contains information about conservation issues and the National Parks Service.
PP 167
PP 513
BIOGRAPHY of E. Raymond Hall
E. Raymond Hall was born on May 11, 1902, in Imes, Kansas. Hall received his A.B. from the University of Kansas in 1924. He accepted a teaching assistantship at the University of California at Berkeley in 1924, and later received both his M.A. degree in 1925 and Ph.D. in 1928 from UC Berkeley. Hall served as curator of mammals at Berkeley from 1927-1944 and was acting director of the museum from 1938-1944. He joined the KU faculty in 1944 as Professor of Zoology and Director of the Museum of Natural History. As director and curator of mammals from 1944-1967, Hall managed a rapid expansion of all collections and successfully lobbied for an addition to the museum which doubled the available space. Hall published more than 340 articles and six books, including the two volume "Mammals of North America". In 1958, Hall was named a Solon E. Summerfield Distinguished Professor. E. Raymond Hall retired in 1972 and died in 1986.
Acquisition Information
Unknown; William Hall, 2011
Restrictions on Access
None
COLLECTION DESCRIPTION
- PP 169
  - (Box Box 1)
    - The Conservation Foundation Letter - February 1971 to 1972 (Folder 1-3)
    - New Horizons: Bulletin for the Junior Museum Field, Spring, Fall, Winter 1955 (Folder 4)
    - Fish and Game news by Harry Lutz (Folder 5-8)
    - Pamphlets (Folder 9)
    - Department of Natural Resources - Madison, Wisconsin, 1973, 1974 (Folder 10)
    - Kofa Wilderness, Arizona (Folder 11)
    - Correspondence - direct (Folder 12-14)
    - Correspondence - organizations (Folder 15-16)
    - The University of California, Berkeley (Folder 17)
    - United States Department of the Interior (Folder 18)
    - Research and Education Association, 1974 (Folder 19)
    - The New York Botanical Garden (Folder 20)
    - The ORV [Off-Road Vehicle] Monitor, June 1974 (Folder 21)
    - Tennessee - Tombigbee Waterway Development Authority, 1972, 1974 (Folder 22)
    - AAAS Bulletin - American Association for the Advancement of Science, 1973, 1974 (Folder 23)
    - Awww - Arizonas for Quality Environment (Folder 24)
    - Arizoo - The Phoenix Zoo, 1973 (Folder 25)
    - Bulletin - American Association for the Advancement of Science, 1974 (Folder 26)
    - Jr. Scholastic - November 15, 1973 (Folder 27)
    - Jax - The Jackson Laboratory, 1974 (Folder 28)
    - Transactions of the San Diego Society of Natural History, 1964, 1966, 1967 (Folder 29)
    - University of Kansas miscellaneous materials (Folder 30-32)
    - Canadian Wildlife Service - reprinted from Canadian Audubon Magazine, 1964 (Folder 33)
    - The Wilderness Society - "Wilderness Hearing Alert" (Folder 34)
    - Conferences - reports, correspondence, presentations (Folder 35-40)
    - Publications, bulletins, newsletters (Folder 41-60)
    - Bulletins, newsletters, journals (Folder 61-65)
    - Environmental issues (Folder 66-67)
    - Miscellaneous materials (Folder 68-70)
    - Pamphlets concerning conservation of waters, wildlife, etc. 1935-1952 (Folder 71-74)
    - Bulletins - Sport fishing institute, conservation news, by-laws and laws of Izaak Walton League, and the State of Indiana, ranging 1946-[19]53, Ross Macy (Folder 75-78)
    - A symposium on the economy of midwest flyways and prairie flora March 5, 1974 (Folder 79-82)
  - (Box Box 2)
    - Job Completion Report - Investigation Projects (Folder 1-3)
    - Awww - Arizonans for quality environment (Folder 4)
    - Outdoor California, 1953, (2) (Folder 5)
    - The George Vanderbilt Foundation News Bulletin (2) (Folder 6)
    - USDA [United States Department of Agriculture] (Folder 7)
    - Division of Vertebrate Morphology - American Society of Zoologists (3), 1973, 1974 (Folder 8)
    - EPA [Environmental Protection Agency] (Folder 9-10)
    - K.A.W. - Kansas Association for Wildlife, Inc. (Folder 11)
    - CORC - Citizens Committee for the Outdoor Recreation Resources Review Commission Report (Folder 12-13)
    - Kansas Academy of Science (Folder 14-15)
    - Wilderness: Imperial Wilderness Proposal - National Wildlife Refuges, Southwest Region (Folder 16)
    - University of Kansas - miscellaneous materials (Folder 17)
    - Correspondence - general (Folder 18)
    - BSCS Newsletter - The Biological Sciences Curriculum Study, 1971 (Folder 19)
    - Publications, bulletins, newsletters (Folder 20-26)
    - The Ozarks Regional Commission, 1971-1972 (Folder 27)
    - Pamphlets (Folder 28)
    - Reports, Publications (Folder 29-33)
    - Publications, bulletins, newsletters (Folder 34-45)
    - Miscellaneous materials (Folder 46-48)
    - National Park Service: maps, brochures, newsletters (Folder 49-60)
    - Turkey: brochures, publications, reports (Folder 61-76)
  - (Box Box 3)
    - National Park Service and Department of the Interior: brochures, newsletters, reports (Folder 1-32)
    - Publications, bulletins, pamphlets, papers (Folder 33-47)
    - America zoo - The legacy of our lands (Folder 48)
    - America 1976: A bicentennial exhibition sponsored by the United States Department of the Interior (Folder 49)
    - Management policies - US Department of the Interior, National Park Service, 1975 (Folder 50-52)
    - Annual Report of the Chief Scientist of the National Park Service, cy 1975 (Book 1)
    - The National Register of Historic Places, 1976 (Book 2)
  - (Box Box 4)
    - Casemates and Cannonballs - Archaeological investigations at Fort Stanwix National Monument by Lee Hanson and Dick Ping Hu (1975) (Folder 1)
    - Tallgrass Prairie Conference - Camp Wood Sept[ember] 13-14, 1975 (Folder 2-3)
    - Resolutions of the Midwest Regional Advisory Committee, July 1973 - September 1976, E.R. Hall rec[eived] Nov[ember] 10, 1976 (Folder 4)
    - National Geographic Society news - received Oct[ober] 4, 1976 (Folder 5)
    - Indiana Dunes National Lakeshore - Indiana (Folder 6)
    - National Park Service - Cuyahoga Valley National Recreation Area (Folder 7-11)
    - National Park Service - News Release, 1976 (Folder 12-13)
    - National Park Service - Newsletter, 1976 (Folder 14-17)
    - Department of the Interior - news release, 1976 (Folder 18-20)
    - Southwest Regional Advisory Committee, 1976 (Folder 21)
    - North Atlantic Regional Advisory Committee, 1976 (Folder 22)
    - Midwest Regional Advisory Committee, 1976 (Folder 23-27)
    - Editorial briefs - The National Park Service as seen by the Nation's Press, 1976 (Folder 28-33)
    - Interpreters Information Exchange - In Touch, 1976 (Folder 34-35)
    - Update: Yosemite Master Plan (Folder 36)
    - List of Pages: WASO pages 1-6 (Folder 37)
    - Standard contract language - Department of the Interior, National Park Service (Folder 38-40)
    - United States Department of the Interior - memoradums, 1976 (Folder 41-49)
    - Department of the Interior and National Park Service - memos, correspondence, publications, papers, bulletins (Folder 50-56)
    - Outdoor News Bulletin - Wildlife Management Institue, 1974-1975 (Folder 57-62)
    - The Greater Prairie Chicken newsletter (2), 1975 (Folder 63)
    - National Parks Magazine (2), 1955, 1963 (Folder 64)
    - Supervivencia magazine (2) (Folder 65)
    - Coyote Research newsletter (2), 1974,1975 (Folder 66)
    - Environmental Protection Agency: technical notes, bulletins, publications (Folder 67-71)
    - Coyotes: reports and memos (Folder 72-73)
    - South Dakota: Department of Game, Fish and Parks - meeting minutes (Folder 74-78)
  - (Box Box 5)
    - South Dakota Cooperative Wildlife Research Unit - Quarterly Report, 1970-1974 (Folder 1-17)
    - Cooperative Extension Service - Kansas State University (Folder 18-28)
    - Publications, pamphlets, bulletins, newsletters (Folder 29-41)
    - Congressional Directory, 93rd Congress, 2nd Session, 1974 (Book 1)
  - (Box Box 6)
    - The Jackson Laboratory - JAX, 1975 (Folder 1)
    - 45th Annual Report 1973-1974 - The Jackson Laboratory (Folder 2)
    - 46th Annual Report 1974-1975 - The Jackson Laboratory (Folder 3)
    - The Kansas Water Resources Board - Kansas Water News (Folder 4)
    - Alaska - Review of business and economic conditions, 1974-1975 (Folder 5-6)
    - National Wildlife Federation - Conservation Report, 1974-1975 (Folder 7-12)
    - Journal of the Washington Academy of Sciences, 1974-1975 (Folder 13-16)
    - "National Environment of Early Food Production North of Mesopotamia" by H.E. Wright, Jr. (Folder 17)
    - Calendar of the Smithsonian Institution, January 1975, November 1974 (Folder 18)
    - Division of Vertebrate Morphology - American Society of Zoologists newsletters, 1974-1975 (Folder 19)
    - Friends of the Sea Otter, 1975 (Folder 20)
    - Publications, pamphlets, newsletters (Folder 21-24)
    - Turkey: Information and newspaper articles (Folder 25)
    - Correspondence 1954-[19]66 (Folder 26-30)
    - Correspondence 1954-[19]70 (Folder 31-39)
    - NPS [National Park Service] directory changes, 1967-[19]69 (Folder 40-45)
    - Pea Ridge Battlefield, 1956 (Folder 46)
    - ERH [E. Raymond Hall] travel, 1955-[19]61 (Folder 47-49)
    - Biology hand book: Kansas and Nebraska (Folder 50)
    - Kansas City Museum 1951-[19]71 (Folder 51-68)
    - Manual for Museums, 1976 (Book 1)
    - Draft Environmental Statement, Onaga Dam and Lake, Vermillion Creek, Pottawatomie County, Kansas, 1973 (Book 2-3)
    - Proceedings of Second Great Plains Wildlife Damage Control Workshop, Kansas State University, 1975 (Book 4)
  - (Box Box 7)
    - Newsletters - Society of Systematic Zoology, 1953-1958, 1964 (Folder 1)
    - Society of Systematic Zoology, 1949 (Folder 2)
    - Society of Systematic Zoology, 1951 (Folder 3-4)
    - Systematic zoology, 1952 (Folder 5-6)
    - Systematic zoology, 1953 (Folder 7-8)
    - Systematic zoology, 1954 (Folder 9-10)
    - Systematic zoology, 1955 (Folder 11-12)
    - Systematic zoology, 1956 (Folder 13-14)
    - Systematic zoology, 1957 (Folder 15-16)
    - Systematic zoology, 1958 (Folder 17-18)
    - Systematic zoology, 1959 (Folder 19-20)
    - Systematic zoology, 1960 (Folder 21-22)
    - Systematic zoology, 1961 (Folder 23-24)
    - Systematic zoology, 1962 (Folder 25-26)
    - Systematic zoology, 1963 (Folder 27-28)
    - Systematic zoology, 1964 (Folder 29-30)
    - Systematic zoology, 1965 (Folder 31-32)
    - Systematic zoology, 1966 (Folder 33)
    - Systematic zoology, 1967 (Folder 34)
    - Systematic zoology, 1970 (Folder 35-36)
    - Systematic zoology, 1971 (Folder 37-38)
    - Systematic zoology, 1972 (Folder 39-40)
  - (Box Box 8)
    - Conservation 1964-[19]65 (Folder 1-13)
    - "The Bounty System in Iowa" by David w. Walter and Paul L. Errington (Folder 14)
    - Guide for a Field Conference on the Tertiary and Pleistocene of Nebraska, 1941 (Folder 15)
    - Kansas Coyote Damage Control Program (Folder 16-18)
    - ZOE - September, 1906-April, 1908 (Folder 19)
    - ZOE - August, 1905 (Folder 20)
    - ZOE - May, 1903 (Folder 21)
    - ZOE - 1900 (Folder 22-23)
    - ZOE: A biological journal, March 1894 (Folder 24)
    - ZOE: A biological journal, 1893 (Folder 25-28)
    - ZOE: A biological journal, 1892 (Folder 29-32)
    - ZOE: A biological journal, 1891 (Folder 33-36)
    - ZOE: A biological journal, 1890 (Folder 37-41)
    - National Parks Service brochures - "A" (Folder 42)
    - Agate Fossil Beds - National Monument, Nebraska (Folder 43)
    - Abraham Lincoln Birthplace - National Historic Site, Kentucky (Folder 44)
    - Acadia National Park - Maine (Folder 45)
    - Adams National Historic Site - Massachusetts (Folder 46)
    - Andrew Johnson National Monument - Tennessee (Folder 47)
    - Antietam National Battlefield Site - Maryland (Folder 48-49)
    - Appomattox Court House National Historic Site - Virginia (Folder 50)
    - Arches National Monument - Utah (Folder 51)
    - Assateague Island National Seashore - Maryland (Folder 52)
    - Aztec Ruins National Monument - New Mexico (Folder 53-54)
    - Buck Island Reef National Monument - Virgin Islands (Folder 55)
    - Bighorn Canyon National Recreation area - Montana (Folder 56)
    - Badlands National Monument - South Dakota (Folder 57-59)
    - Bent's Old Fort National Historic Site - Colorado (Folder 60)
    - Bandelier National Monument - New Mexico (Folder 61-62)
    - Big Bend National Park - Texas (Folder 63-64)
    - Big Hole National Battlefield - Montana (Folder 65)
    - Black Canyon of the Gunnison National Monument - Colorado (Folder 66)
    - Blue Ridge Parkway - Virginia and North Carolina (Folder 67-69)
    - Booker T. Washington National Monument - Virginia (Folder 70)
    - Brice's Cross Roads National Battlefield Site - Mississippi (Folder 71)
    - Bryce Canyon National Park - Utah (Folder 72-73)
    - Boating Regulations in the National Park System (Folder 74)
  - (Box Box 9)
    - Miscellaneous "C" (Folder 1)
    - Chesapeake and Ohio Canal, District of Columbia and Ohio (Folder 2)
    - Chickamauga Battlefield National Military Park, Georgia and Tennessee (Folder 3)
    - Chimney Rock National Historic Site, Nebraska (Folder 4)
    - Curecanti recreation area, Colorado (Folder 5)
    - Chiricahua National Monument - Arizona (Folder 6-7)
    - Christiansted National Historic Site - St. Croix, Virgin Islands (Folder 8)
    - City of Refuge National Historical Park - Hawaii (Folder 9-10)
    - Colonial Parkway - Colonial National Historic Park, Virginia (Folder 11)
    - Colorado National Monument - Colorado (Folder 12-13)
    - Coronado National Memorial - Arizona (Folder 14-15)
    - Coulee Dam National Recreation Area - Washington (Folder 16-17)
    - Canyon de Chelly National Monument - Arizona (Folder 18)
    - Cape Cod National Seashore - Massachusetts (Folder 19-20)
    - Cape Hatteras National Seashore Recreational Area - North Carolina (Folder 21-23)
    - Cape Henry Memorial - Virginia (Folder 24)
    - Capitol Reef National Monument - Utah (Folder 25)
    - Capulin Mountain National Monument - New Mexico (Folder 26)
    - Carlsbad Cavern National Park - New Mexico (Folder 27-29)
    - Craters of the Moon National Monument - Idaho (Folder 30)
    - Cabrillo National Monument - California (Folder 31)
    - Cedar Breaks National Monument - Utah (Folder 32)
    - Castilo de San Marcos National Monument - Florida (Folder 33)
    - Carpenters Hall - Independence National Historic Park, Pennsylvania (Folder 34)
    - Casa Grande Ruins National Monument - Arizona (Folder 35)
    - Channel Islands National Monument - California (Folder 36)
    - Chalmette National Historical Park - Louisiana (Folder 37-38)
    - Chaco Canyon National Monument - New Mexico (Folder 39)
    - Custis-Lee Mansion - The Robert E. Lee Memorial, Virginia (Folder 40-41)
    - Custer Battlefield National Monument - Montana (Folder 42)
    - Cumberland Gap National Historical Park - Kentucky, Virginia, Tennessee (Folder 43)
    - Crater Lake National Park - Oregon (Folder 44-47)
    - The Cherry Blossoms, Washington, D.C. (Folder 48)
    - Cowpens National Battlefield Site - South Carolina (Folder 49)
    - Miscellaneous "D" National Parks (Folder 50)
    - De Soto National Memorial, Florida (Folder 51)
    - Dinosaur National Monument, Colorado and Utah (Folder 52-54)
    - Devils Tower National Monument, Wyoming (Folder 55)
    - Devils Postpile National Monument, Califronia (Folder 56)
    - Death Valley National Monument, California (Folder 57-59)
    - Everglades National Park, Florida (Folder 60-61)
    - El Morro National Monument, New Mexico (Folder 62)
    - Emerald Mound, Mississippi (Folder 63)
    - Effigy Mounds National Monument, Iowa (Folder 64)
    - Edison Laboratory National Monument, New Jersey (Folder 65-66)
    - Mr. Ford's Theatre, Washington, D.C. (Folder 67)
    - Florida Keys Wilderness Proposal (Folder 68)
    - Fall River Dam and Reservoir, Kansas (Folder 69)
    - Frederick Douglass Home, Washington D.C. (Folder 70)
    - Fort McHenry National Monument, Maryland (Folder 71)
    - Fredericksburg and Spotsylvania National Military Park, Virginia (Folder 72-73)
    - Fort Washington, Maryland (Folder 74)
    - Fort Vancouver National Historic Site, Washington (Folder 75)
    - Fort Union National Monument, New Mexico (Folder 76-77)
    - Fort Sumter National Monument, South Carolina (Folder 78)
    - Fort Smith National Historic Site, Arkansas (Folder 79)
    - Fort Raleigh National Historic Site, North Carolina (Folder 80)
    - Fort McHenry National Monument and Historic Shrine, Maryland (Folder 81)
    - Fort Necessity National Battlefield, Pennsylvania (Folder 82)
    - Fort Pulaski National Monument, Georgia (Folder 83)
    - Federal Hall National Memorial, New York City (Folder 84)
    - Fire Island National Seashore, New York (Folder 85)
    - Flaming Gorge Recreation Area, Wyoming and Utah (Folder 86)
    - Ford's Theatre and the House Where Lincoln Died, Washington, D.C. (Folder 87)
    - Fort Caroline National Memorial, Florida (Folder 88)
    - Fort Clatsop National Memorial, Florida (Folder 89)
    - Fort Davis National Historic Site, Texas (Folder 90)
    - Fort Donelson National Military Park, Tennessee (Folder 91)
    - Fort Frederica National Monument, Georgia (Folder 92)
    - Fort Jefferson National Monument, Florida (Folder 93)
    - Fort Laramie National Historic Site, Wyoming (Folder 94-95)
    - Fort Matanzas National Monument, Florida (Folder 96)
    - Gila Cliff Dwellings (Folder 97)
    - Glacial Bay National Monument, Alaska (Folder 98)
    - Glen Canyon National Recreation Area (Folder 99)
    - Grand Canyon National Park, Arizona (Folder 100-103)
    - Grand Portage National Monument, Minnesota (Folder 104)
    - Grand Teton National Park, Wyoming (Folder 105-108)
    - Great Sand Dunes National Monument, Colorado (Folder 109-110)
  - (Box Box 10)
    - Great Smoky Mountains National Park, Tennessee and North Carolina (Folder 1-4)
    - Guilford Courthouse, North Carolina (Folder 5)
    - Gettysburg National Milirary Park, Pennsylvania (Folder 6-8)
    - Glacier National Park, Montana (Folder 9-12)
    - George Washington Carver National Monument, Missouri (Folder 13)
    - George Washington Memorial Parkway (Folder 14)
    - General Grant National Memorial, New York City (Folder 15)
    - George Washington Birthplace National Monument, Virginia (Folder 16-18)
    - Herbert Hoover National Historic Site, Iowa (Folder 19)
    - Hubbell Trading Post National Historic Site, Arizona (Folder 20)
    - Hovenweep National Monument, Utah (Folder 21)
    - Hot Springs National Park, Arkansas (Folder 22-23)
    - Horseshoe Bend National Military Park, Alabama (Folder 24)
    - Hopewell Village National Historic Site, Pennsylvania (Folder 25-27)
    - Homestead National Monument, Nebraska (Folder 28)
    - Home of Franklin D. Roosevelt National Historic Site, Hyde Park, New York (Folder 29)
    - Harper's Ferry National Monument, West Virginia (Folder 30-31)
    - Hampton National Historic Site, Maryland (Folder 32)
    - Haleakala National Park, Island of Maui, Hawaii (Folder 33-34)
    - Hawaii Volcanoes National Park, Island of Hawaii, Hawaii (Folder 35-38)
    - Independence Historical Park, Pennsylvania (Folder 39-40)
    - Isle Royal National Park, Michigan (Folder 41-42)
    - Indiana Dunes, National Lakeshore Project (Folder 43)
    - Islandia National Park committee, Florida (Folder 44)
    - International Office for the Protection of Nature (Folder 45)
    - Jefferson National Expansion Memorial, St. Louis, Missouri (Folder 46)
    - John Muir National Historic Site, California (Folder 47)
    - Johnstown Flood National Memorial, Allegheny Portage Railroad National Historic Site, Pennsylvania (Folder 48)
    - Jackson Hole, Wyoming (Folder 49)
    - Jewell Cave National Monument, South Dakota (Folder 50)
    - Joshua Tree National Monument, California (Folder 51)
    - Jamestown, Virginia (Folder 52-55)
    - John Fitzgerald National Historic Site, Massachusetts (Folder 56)
    - Kenilworth Aquatic Gardens, Washington, D.C. (Folder 57)
    - Katmai National Monument, Alaska (Folder 58)
    - Kennewas Mountain National Battlefield Park (Folder 59)
    - Kings Mountain National Military Park, South Carolina (Folder 60)
    - Miscellaneous "L" (Folder 61)
    - Lafayette Park, Washington, D.C. (Folder 62)
    - Lake Mead-Lake Mohave National Recreation Area, Arizona-Nevada (Folder 63-65)
    - Lassen Volcanic National Park, California (Folder 66-67)
    - Lava Beds National Monument, California (Folder 68-69)
    - Lehman Caves National Monument, Nevada (Folder 70)
    - Lincoln Boyhood National Memorial, Indiana (Folder 71)
    - The Lincoln Museum and the House Where Lincoln Died (Folder 72)
    - Lincoln Memorial, Washington, D.C. (Folder 73)
    - Miscellaneous "M" (Folder 74)
    - Minute Man National Historical Park, Massachusetts (Folder 75)
    - Muir Woods National Monument, California (Folder 76)
    - Mount Vernon Memorial Highway (Folder 77)
    - Mount Rushmore National Monument, South Dakota (Folder 78)
    - Mount Rainer National Park, Washington (Folder 79-82)
    - Mount McKinley National Park, Alaska (Folder 83-85)
    - Mound City Group National Mounument, Ohio (Folder 86)
    - Moses H. Cone Memorial Park, Blue Ridge Parkway, North Carolina (Folder 87)
    - Morristwon National Historical Park, New Jersey (Folder 88)
    - Moore's Creek National Military Park, North Carolina (Folder 89)
    - Montezuma Castle National Monument, Arizona (Folder 90-91)
    - Mesa Verde National Park, Colorado (Folder 92-94)
    - Meriweather Lewis Park, Tennessee (Folder 95)
    - McLoughlin House National Historic Site, Oregon (Folder 96)
    - Manassas National Battlefield Park, Virginia (Folder 97-98)
    - Mammoth Cave National Park, Kentucky (Folder 99-102)
  - (Box Box 11)
    - Miscellaneous "N" (Folder 1)
    - National Park System brochures (Folder 2)
    - New York Botanical Garden (Folder 3)
    - Nez Pearce National Historical Park, Idaho (Folder 4)
    - Navajo National Monument, Arizona (Folder 5)
    - Natural Bridges National Monument, Utah (Folder 6)
    - Natchez Trace Parkway, Tennessee, Alabama, Mississippi (Folder 7)
    - National Capital Parks (Folder 8-10)
    - Miscellaneous "O" (Folder 11)
    - Ozark National Scenic Riverways, Missouri (Folder 12)
    - Oregon Caves National Monument, Oregon (Folder 13)
    - Organ Pipe Cactus National Monument, Arizona (Folder 14)
    - Olympic National Park, Washington (Folder 15-19)
    - Ocmulgee National Monument, Georgia (Folder 20)
    - Miscellaneous "P" (Folder 21)
    - Puerto Rico (Folder 22-23)
    - Point Park Lookout Mountain and Chattanooga Battlefields, Georgia and Tennessee (Folder 24)
    - Padre Island National Seashore, Texas (Folder 25)
    - Pea Ridge National Military Park, Arkansas (Folder 26)
    - Perry's Victory and International Peace Memorial National Monument, Ohio (Folder 27)
    - Petersburg National Military Park, Virginia (Folder 28-30)
    - Petrifried Forest National Monument, Arizona (Folder 31-33)
    - Pinnacles National Monument, California (Folder 34-35)
    - Pipe Spring National Monument, Arizona (Folder 36)
    - Pipestone National Monument, Minnesota (Folder 37)
    - Platt National Park, Oklahoma (Folder 38-39)
    - Point Reyes National Seashore, California (Folder 40)
    - Prince William Forest Park, Virginia (Folder 41-42)